Be careful.
So you are really sick, Sixth Brother.
I thought you were
with Mr. Su.
I've been busy with official evaluations recently.
I gave orders not to be disturbed.
I didn't expect to neglect you, Third Brother.
I'm really sorry.
You guys are really something.
This is my mansion.
When is Third Brother not allowed here?
You're making a fuss over nothing.
I wonder what brings you here, Third Brother.
Why not have a cup of tea before you go?
My beloved wife has been away for days.
I have missed you so much.
I'll take my leave.
Xiyao.
Why did you come back with me,
grind ink and make soup for me?
We are husband and wife.
It is my duty to do so.
You touched Su Zhiye with this hand today.
It displeased me greatly.
I just casually pushed him aside.
I still have things to do.
Go back and rest first.
I do have a favor to ask of you.
According to our Rouran customs,
I am supposed to take you back for a week after our wedding.
If it's inconvenient for you,
I can go back by myself.
What if I refuse?
I'll go back and rest first.
I was serious when I said we are husband and wife.
I wasn't rejecting you just now.
I was just a little nervous.
Xiyao.
Don't go back.
I can leave with you.
If you want to return to Rouran,
I can accompany you.
It's good that you're back.
I have no excuse.
Xiyao.
Before you appeared,
I never thought about
besides the supreme throne,
what else I wanted.
But now,
I also want you.
Look at your hands.
I know what you want to do,
and I know what you have done.
The ridiculous thing is,
I'm still here waiting for you.
I was afraid you wouldn't come back after seeing Su Zhiye.
You don't blame me?
Are you really so naive to think
that Yuwen Jingxuan will be fine after getting the Soul Jade back?
That I have no other way?
That everything will be at peace?
You're bleeding.
Stop picking it up.
You too.
This is the Soul Jade Xiyao got back from Yuwen Jia.
Where is he?
He went back.
Zhiluo, Miss Tang.
Jingxuan.
Miss Tang, Jingxuan.